Guide to the Thomas Cover Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Thomas Cover papers
circa 1964-2011
SC1129
Cover, Thomas, 1938-2012.
73.5 Linear feet and 128 megabytes
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
Born in San Bernardino, California, on August 7, 1938, Thomas M. Cover received a B.S. in physics from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology in 1960, and M.S. and Ph.D. degrees, both in electrical engineering, from Stanford in 1961 and 1964, respectively.
Cover joined the faculty at the Stanford School of Engineering in 1964, becoming a professor in 1972. He directed Stanford's Information Systems Laboratory from 1988 to 1996. In 1994, he was named the Kwoh-Ting Li Professor of Electrical Engineering and Statistics.
In 1990, the Information Theory Society of the IEEE awarded him the Claude E. Shannon Award, the highest honor for lifetime achievement in information theory. In 1997, the IEEE awarded him the Richard W. Hamming medal for "fundamental work in information theory, statistics and pattern recognition."
Cover was past president of the IEEE Information Theory Society. He was elected to the National Academy of Engineering, and named as a Fellow by the American Association for the Advancement of Science, the Institute of Mathematical Statistics and the IEEE. In 2003, he was elected to the American Academy of Arts and Sciences.
Access Terms
Engineering--Study and teaching.; Information theory.; Stanford University--Faculty housing.; Universities and colleges--Faculty.
Collection Contents
- Teaching, Series 1
  - Courses
    - Stat 376, 1997-98 (Box 1)
    - Stat 217, 1998 autumn (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - EE 370, 1998 autumn (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - EE 376A, 1998-99 winter (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - EE 376B, 1998-99 spring (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Stat 218, 1999-00 spring (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - EE 376B, 2000-01 spring (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Stat 218, 2000-01 spring (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - EE 376A, 2000-01 winter (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Stat 319, 2000 autumn (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - EE 376B, 2002-03 spring (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - EE 376A, 2002-03 winter (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - EE 376B, 2004-05 spring (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - EE 376A, 2004-05 Winter (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - EE 376B, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Stats 50, 2007 spring (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - EE 376A, 2007-08 winter (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - EE 376B, 2008-09 spring (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - EE 376A, 2008-09 winter (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Stats 50, 2007-08 spring (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - EE 376A: notes, questionnaires, handouts, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - EE 376A: lectures (two folders), 2011 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - EE 376B: extra problems (book), [undated] (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - EE376B: topics, 2010 spring (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Stat 363, 1972-75 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - EE 477, ca.1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Physics 230, various dates (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - AP 255 QT: Quant. Info Yamamoto, 2000 spring (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - EE 376B homework sets, notes, varies (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - EE 376 B copies of notes, 2005 spring (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - EE 376B, 2009 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - EE 376B, 2009 April 7 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - EE 376B, 2009 spring (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - EE 376B, various dates (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - EE 376B, various dates (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - EE 376B, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Wednesday research seminar, 2011 aut; 2012 winter (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Wednesday research seminar, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 2011 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - MS/PhD advisees, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - EE 376A, 2011 winter (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Info theory course notes, 1985 March 12 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - EE 376A problems, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - [unlabeled] (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Stat 217, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Physics of Info, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - [unlabeled], 2001 Feb 1 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - EE 376B, 2001 april (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Stat 391 Literature of Statistics, 2000 autumn (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Stat 218, 2001 spring (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Stat 218 Lectures 2,3,4, 2001 april (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Stat 218 Lectures 2,3,4, 2001 april (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - EE 278, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - teaching evaluations, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - EE 478, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - EE 376, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Jan 5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Jan 7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Jan 12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Jan 14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Jan 19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Jan 21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Jan 26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Jan 28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Feb 2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Feb 4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Feb 9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Feb 11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Feb 18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Feb 23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 Feb 25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 March 2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 March 4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 March 9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1999 March 11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Jan 14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Jan 16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Jan 21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Jan 23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Jan 28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Jan 30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Feb 4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Feb 6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Feb 11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Feb 13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Feb 20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Feb 25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Feb 27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Mar 4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Mar 6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - EE 376A, 1997 Mar 11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
    - Stats 136, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Game Theory S. Messing Notes, 1978 Spring (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Stats 136 Danielle Beaudry, 1974 Autumn (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Game Theory Stats 136 HW + Solns, 1978 Spring (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Game Theory Math 144 Feng Notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Stats 136 Game Theory Notes by Michael Minicka, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Game Theory Freguson Notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Stats 136 Notes, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Stats 136 Notes, 1972, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Mathematical Games, 1977 March (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Scientific American, 1983 May (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Competitive Bidding and Proprietary Information, 1982 Oct. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Some Results on Max-Min Pursiut Abstract, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Lion and Man: A Bounded Pursuit Game by James Flynn, 1970 Oct. 2 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - A Weighted Voting Model, 1980 Jan. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - The Power of Voting Blocs: An Example, 1977 Jan. 1 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Condorcet Social Choice Functions, 1976 Sept. 23 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Group Decision Devices, 1977 May (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Letters to the Editor, circa 1982 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Mathematical Methods of Economics, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - LP Duality, 1987 May (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - The South American Game, 1977 Jan. (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Num and Other Oriented Graph Games by Andrew M. Gleason, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - All Games Bright and Beautiful, 1977 June-July (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Convexity and Mixtures, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Mathematical games by Martin Gardner, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - A Stochastic Search Game, 1978 Jan. 1 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Game Theory Stat 136 Office Hours, 1978 Spring (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Values of Large Games II: Oceanic Games, 1978 Nov. (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Artificial Intelligence and the Iterated Prisoner's Dilemma, 1978 Feb. (Box 13, Folder 31a)
    - The Evolution of Cooperation, 1981 March 27 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Class Notes, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Review Notes, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Stat 218, 200-2001 Spring (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Stat 218, 1999-2000 Spring (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Stat 218, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Stat 218, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - EE278, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Stat 119, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Notes, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Stat 119 Class Notes, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Stat 219/220, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Stat 220 Class Notes, 1981 Spring (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Info & Stat, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Portfolio Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Unlabeled Binder (Physics, Quantum Mechanics), 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - ITMANET Files, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Portfolio Theory, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Portfolio Papers, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Portfolio Refs, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Portfolio Theory Reprints - Samuelson Correspondence, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - EE478, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - EE 478 - Topics in Information Theory, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - EE 478 - Special Topics in Information Theory, Autumn 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - EE377, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - EE377, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - EE377 Stat 361 Lectures and Homeworks, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - EE 377/Stat 361 Lectures, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - EE377 (Handouts), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - EE377 (Notes), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - EE377, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Stat 217 - Problems and Outlines, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Stat 217 - Misc, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Stat 217 - Lectures, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Stat 217 Handouts, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Stat 217 - Questionnaires, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Stat 218 - Misc. Notes, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Stat 218, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Stat 218 - Loose Stuff, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Stat 218 - Backup Notes, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Stat 218 - Problems, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Stat 218, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Stat 218 - Notes by J. Bruck, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Stat 218, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Stat 218 - Notes, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Stat 218, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Stat 218, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Stat 218, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Stat 218 - Student Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Stat 218 - Homework, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Stat 218 - Student Survey, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Stat 218 - File and Background, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Stat 218 - Notes, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Stat 218 - Misc., 1995 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Stat 218 - Lectures, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Stat 218 - Lectures, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - EE376B Misc., 1991-2005 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - EE376B, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - EE376B, Spring 2010 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - EE376B, Spring 2001 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - EE376B, Spring 1996 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - EE376B, Spring 2009 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - EE376A, Winter 2007-2008 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - EE376A, Winter 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - STAT200, Autumn 1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - STAT200 Into. Stat. Inference, Autumn 1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - STAT 119/219, Winter 1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - STAT200, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - STAT200, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - STAT200, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Math100 Math in Sports, Undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Math100 Math in Sports, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Mathematics in Sports Tom Cover, Autumn 1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Stat 50, Spring 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Stats 50, Autumn 2009 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Sports Papers, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Sports Statistics, Undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Math 100, Winter 1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Stat 100 Math in Sports, Autumn 1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Stats 50 MCS 100, Spring 2008 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Stats 50/MCS 100, Autumn 2009 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Stats 50 Talks, May 2007 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Stat 50, Spring 1998 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Stat 50, Spring 1998 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Stat 50, Spring 2000 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - 0
    - Stat 236A, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Stat 236B, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Literature of Statistics: STAT 319, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Yiynan She, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Yuxue Jin, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Stat 319 Class List, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Zhen Wei, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Hua Zhou (Stein's Method), 2006 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Ping Li (dropped), 2006 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Hoefling, Hoger, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Andres Eckner, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Rudy Angeles, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Kshitij Khare, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Stat 361-EE377, 1982 Spring (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Pattern Recognition, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - EE 376A Documents, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Course Reader EE 376A, 2010 Winter (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Homework
    - Old information theory notes, 1961-62 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - EE 252n homework sets, 1965 fall (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - EE 254 homework sets, 1964 autumn (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - EE 352, 1964 summer (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - EE 265 Berlekamp, 1964 autumn (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - EE 253 b homework sets, 1966 spring (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - EE 254 homework sets, 1966 autumn (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - EE 254 homework sets (second folder), 1966 autumn (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - EE 253 A lecture notes, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - EE 253 b homework sets, 1967 spring (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - EE 253 A homework sets (originals), 1967 winter (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - EE 376 homework sets, 1967 autumn (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - EE 479 homework sets, 1968 spring (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - EE 377 homework sets, 1968 winter (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - EE 376 homework sets, 1968 autumn (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - EE 376 homework sets (second folder), 1968 autumn (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - EE 376 Information Theory [homework sets], 1969 autumn (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - EE 376 homework sets, 1969 autumn (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - EE 377 B homework sets, 1969 spring (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - EE 377A homework sets, 1969 winter (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - EE 377 B homework sets, 1970 spring (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - EE 377A homework sets, 1970 winter (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Stat 361 B/EE 377 A Classification and pattern recognition: homework sets, 1971 spring (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - EE 363 A System theory: determinis. Homework sets, 1971 winter (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Stat 116 E, 1973 autumn (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Stat 363/EE 378 homework, 1973 spring (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - EE 377, Stat 361 Classif. & P. recognition, 1973 winter (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Stat 136, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - EE 375 (seminar), 1974 spring (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Stat 363 (EE 477), 1974 spring (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - EE 376, 1974 winter (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - EE 376 Information theory, 1974 winter (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Stat 236 A Mathematical statistics, 1975 autumn (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Stat 363 Statistical complexity, 1975 spring (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Stat 236-B Mathematical statistics, 1976 winter (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - EE 376 Information theory, 1976 winter (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - EE 376 A Information theory, 1980 autumn (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Homework 1981 [Stat 116, final exam], 1981 autumn (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - EE 376 A, 1981 autumn (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - EE 478 Topics in statistical sig. processing, 1976 autumn (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Homework 1982 [Tau Beta Pi survey], 1982 autumn (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Stat 361/EE 377 Stat. pattern recognition, 1982 spring (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - EE 377/Stat 361, 1982 spring (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - EE 376 A Information theory, 1982 autumn (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - EE 392 B Stat. & information theory, 1982 spring (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Stat 202 Game theory, 1983 autumn (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Stat 119/219 Stat inference, 1983 winter (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - EE 392 H/Stat 362 information and statistics, 1983 spring (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - EE 376 A Information theory, 1984 autumn (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - EE 376 A Information theory [binder], 1984 autumn (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Stat 218, 1984 winter (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - EE 376 B Information theory, 1984 winter (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - EE 377/Stat 361 Stat. pattern recog., 1984 spring (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - EE 376 A Information theory, 1985 autumn (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Stat 200 Intro Stat. inference, 1985 autumn (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - EE 376 B Information theory, 1985 winter (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - EE 376 B Information theory, 1986 winter (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Stat 364 Topics in gambling and investing, 1986 spring (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - EE 376 A/Stat 376 Information theory, 1987 autumn (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - EE 376 A/Stat 376 Information theory [binder], 1987 autumn (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Stat 218, 1988 spring (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - EE 376 B, 1988 winter (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - EE 376 A, 1988 fall (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - EE 376 B, 1989 winter (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Stat 218, 1989 spring (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - EE 392 M EE 392N/Stat 392, 1989/90 spring (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - EE 376 A, 1990/91 autumn (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - EE 376 B, 1990/91 winter (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Math Comp Sci 100, 1990/91 winter (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - EE 278, 1991/92 autumn (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - EE 370, 1991 autumn (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Stat 218, 1991/92 winter (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - EE 376 A, 1992/93 winter (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - EE 376 B, 1992/93 spring (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Stat 218, 1994/95 winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - EE 376 A, 1994/95 winter (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - EE 376 B, 1994/95 spring (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - EE 370, 1995/96 autumn (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Stat 200, 1995/96 winter (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - EE 478, 1995/96 spring (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - EE 376 A, 1996/97 winter (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - EE 376 B, 1996/97 spring (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Publications, Series 2
  - Partially controllable random walk, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Classification and generalization capabilities of linear threshold units, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Generalization and classification capabilities of linear threshold units (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Geometrical and statistical properties of linear threshold devices (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Geometrical and statistical properties of systems of linear inequalities with applications in pattern recognition (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Geometrical & statis. properties of systems of linear inequalities …, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Linear rankings of finite-dimensional patterns (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Behavior of sequential predictors of binary sequences (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The probability that a random game is unfair (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Nearest neighbor pattern classification (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Review of "Optimum seeking methods", 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The number of linearly inducible orderings of points, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Linear separability of random points on a hypersphere, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Linear separability of random vectors, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Geometrical probability & random points on a hypersphere, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Geometrical probability & random points on a hypersphere (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - A note on the two-armed bandit problem with finite memory (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Estimation by the nearest neighbor rule, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Convergence rates for the nearest neighbor procedures, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Rates of convergence for nearest neighbor procedures, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Rates of convergence for nearest neighbor procedures" T.Cover. (1st annual Hawaiian Internat. Conf. on Systems Theory), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Capacity problems for linear machines, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "The two armed bandit problem with time-invariant finite memory" M. Hellman & T. Cover (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Comments on the paper "Asymptotically optimal …", 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "Hypothesis testing with finite statistics" T. Cover (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "Learning in pattern recognition" T. Cover (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "Finite memory hypothesis testing: comments on a critique" M. Hellman and T. Cover (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "Learning with finite memory" M. Hellman & T. Cover (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Automata in random media, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "Comments on automata in random media" M. Hellman & T. Cover (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - "On memory saved by randomization" T. Cover & M. Hellman (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Broadcast channels: paper submitted to IEEE IT, 1972 Jan (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Admissibility properties of Gilbert's encoding for ..., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "A hierarchy of probability density function estimates" T. Cover (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - "On determining the irrationality of the mean of a random variable" Rev. June 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Enumerative source encoding, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - A review of recent results on learning with finite memory, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Generalization on patterns using Kolmogorov complexity, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Review of five books in pattern recognition, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Universal gambling schemes and the complexity measures of Kolmogorov and Chaitin (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - The best of two independent measurements are not the two best, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Cooperative broadcasting, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - revision Cooperative broadcasting, 1973 Nov (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Some advances in broadcast channels (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Open problems in Info theory, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - An achievable rate region for the broadcast channel (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - A finite memory test of the irrationality of the parameter of a coin T. Cover and P. Hirschler (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - A proof of the data compression theorem of Slepian and Wolf for ergodic sources (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Optimal finite memory learning algorithms for the finite sample problem, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Topics in statistical pattern recognition (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Comments on Stone's paper, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Compound Bayes predictors, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - On the possible orderings in the measurement selection problem, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - A compound sequential Bayes predictor for sequences with an empirical Markov structure, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - #2 version: Compound Bayes predictors for sequences with apparent Markov structure, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - "An offensive statistic for baseball" T. Cover & C. Keilers, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - A convergent gambling estimate of the entropy of English, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Some equivalences between Shannon entropy and Kolmogorov complexity, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 58)